search4passion.com 2012-12-29

# 

## Privacy Policy

Search4Passion.com is in partnership with Mate1.com. Search4Passion.com captures and passes your information on to the Mate1.com system. In order to complete this transaction, Search4Passion.com requires that you provide your e-mail address, zip code, age and gender. We also collect your IP address and related information from your browser, and we use cookies to remember your computer when you return to the site. 

If you choose to upgrade your Mate1.com membership for a fee, we require your name, credit card information and billing address in order to process the transaction. No other personally identifiable information is required for the site, although your personal profile may include additional information about yourself, including photographs. 

All personally identifiable information collected by Search4Passion.com is only used in connection with the services offered at Mate1.com. As a part of our service we sometimes post and feature photographs provided by our members in print and online, accompanied by the member's profile. Mate1.com does not share your personally identifiable information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes. We may share your information with our affiliates, which are companies controlled by, controlling or under common control with Mate1.com. 

We may engage unaffiliated third parties to assist with services related to the website, including but not limited to hosting, marketing and promotional activities, technical support and credit card processing services. These third parties are obligated to keep the information secure and confidential and must use the information only in connection with providing services to Mate1.com. 

Mate1.com may, from time to time, communicate with you regarding customer service or to inform you of special offers that we believe you may be interested in. At that time we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out and not to receive further information about that special offer, or other similar offers. 

The information collected by Mate1.com may be transferred in connection with the sale or merger of the company, or a sale of substantially all the assets, or in connection with a bankruptcy. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with court orders or with requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the rights, property, safety of our website and other users of the site. 

If you have any questions about this statement, please contact us via the contact form or direct your mail to: 

We may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at unsubscribe@Search4Passion.com. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to Search4Passion.com, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request. 

If you prefer for us not to provide your name and email or postal address to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact us at unsubscribe@Search4Passion.com. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 10/30/2008. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect on this site.
